[{
        "question": "What is india's capital",
        "a": "New Delhi",
        "b": "Mumbai",
        "c": "Chennai",
        "d": "Bhubaneswar",
        "answer": "New Delhi"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is The most used language in ML",
        "a": "JavaScript",
        "b": "C",
        "c": "C++",
        "d": "Python",
        "answer": "Python"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is The most used language in Web Dev",
        "a": "JavaScript",
        "b": "C",
        "c": "C++",
        "d": "Python",
        "answer": "JavaScript"
    },
    {
        "question": "Founder of kiit",
        "a": "Honourable",
        "b": "Chutya",
        "c": "Achutya",
        "d": "Achutya Samanta",
        "answer": "Achutya Samanta"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is The most crowded branch in kiit",
        "a": "CSE",
        "b": "ETC",
        "c": "IT",
        "d": "Law",
        "answer": "CSE"
    },
    {
        "question": "How can we describe an array in the best possible way",
        "a": "The Array shows a hierarchical structure",
        "b": "Arrays are immutable",
        "c": "Container that stores the elements of similar types",
        "d": "The Array is not a data structure",
        "answer": "Container that stores the elements of similar types"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of the following is the process of inserting an element in the stack?",
        "a": "Insert",
        "b": "Add",
        "c": "Push",
        "d": "None of the above",
        "answer": "push"
    },
    {
        "question": "When the user tries to delete the element from the empty stack then the condition is said to be a",
        "a": "Overflow",
        "b": "Underflow",
        "c": "Garbage collection",
        "d": "None of the above",
        "answer": "Underflow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the national crush of india",
        "a": "Rashmika",
        "b": "Anupama",
        "c": "Kiara",
        "d": "Struggle",
        "answer": "Rashmika"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which game is the GOAT",
        "a": "GTA San andreas",
        "b": "Mario",
        "c": "Mortal Kombat",
        "d": "Minecraft",
        "answer": "GTA San andreas"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of the following is not the application of the stack data structure",
        "a": "Asynchronous data transfer",
        "b": "Backtracking",
        "c": "Reversal",
        "d": "Recursion",
        "answer": "Asynchronous data transfer"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which data structure is mainly used for implementing the recursive algorithm",
        "a": "Stack",
        "b": "Queue",
        "c": "Array",
        "d": "Tree",
        "answer": "Stack"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is another name for the circular queue among the following options",
        "a": "Square buffer",
        "b": "Rectangular buffer",
        "c": "Ring buffer",
        "d": "None of the above",
        "answer": "None of the above"
    }
]